我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来
To the outside world,
我只是个普通的鉴证专员
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
But secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
但是我在时间中迷失了
But I became lost in time.
我的朋友们用尽了一切办法才把我救回来
It took everything in my friends' power to bring me back,
但我们的世界也因此出现了新的威胁
and in doing so our world was opened up to new threats.
我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
And I'm the only one fast enough to stop them.
我是闪电侠
I am the Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on the Flash...
我没有杀克利福德·迪沃
I didn't kill Clifford DeVoe.
骗到你们了吧
Tricked ya!
巴里  他们抓了个人质
Barry, they took a hostage.
-抓了谁  -你爸
- Well, who'd he take? - Your dad.
准备好迎接我的超级战衣了
I'm ready for my supersuit.
这块布就是你的超级战衣
This tarp is your supersuit.
这是什么  小狗的雨衣
What is this, a puppy's raincoat?
干得漂亮  菜鸟
Nice job, rookie.
我不会做逃亡者  如果被定罪
I won't be a fugitive. If I'm convicted,
我不会跑
I'm not going to run.
被告有罪
We find the defendant guilty.
亨利·艾伦曾
住于此
这里失控了
We're losing control of the place,
丢烟雾弹
drop grenades.
投放烟雾弹
Deploy smoke grenades!
支援  我们需要支援
Backup, we need backup!
他们回去了  锁上
They're back in. Lock it down.
我们走  出去
Let's move. Move out.
巴里也来这里了
闪 电 侠
第四季
第十一集
告诉我们你要怎样
Fine, just tell us what you want.
我要你们撤退  不然我就引爆这玩意儿
I want you to back off, or I will detonate this thing.
冷静  今天没必要弄得有人受伤
Okay, calm down, nobody needs to get hurt today.
按我说的做
You just follow instructions,
每个人就能看到明天的太阳  懂吗
and everybody here gets to live to see the sunshine tomorrow. Right?
对了  最好别让我看到闪电侠
And I'd better not see The Flash, either.
首先  我需要一辆车
All right, first, I want a car.
环保的  比如丰田普锐斯
Something eco-friendly, like a Prius.
好  这个我们可以满足
Okay, we can do that.
很好
Good. Uh, right.
现在第二点
Now second.
我要一架飞机  私人飞机
Uh, I want a plane, okay? A private plane.
还有一份沙拉  我在计算卡路里
Okay, and a salad, all right? I'm counting calories.
好  需要花一小时时间去安排
Okay, it's going to take us an hour to arrange that.
你最好快点
You better hurry up,
因为3个人质没多少时间
because these hostages don't have much time.
应该要一份牛排的  老兄
Should have gone with a steak, pal.
因为那是接下来5到10年内
'Cause it's the last decent meal you're getting
你能够吃到的最好的一顿了
for the next five to ten years.
你是谁
Who the hell are you?
你友好的邻居超级英雄
Your friendly neighborhood superhero.
你可以叫我
You can call me...
先生
Mr...
等等
One second.
伙计们  现在是我的关键时刻
Guys, this is a huge moment for me.
我的名字是什么
What's my name?
我还在想你没名字能撑多久呢
I was wondering where you were going with that.
我的人质去哪儿了
Hey, hey, where are my hostages?
卫生间
Uh, bathroom break.
他们憋不住了
They just couldn't hold it anymore.
不过别担心  他们很安全
Don't worry, though, they're totally safe.
别过来  怪胎
Get back, freak.
怪胎  棍子和石头会弄折我的骨头的  兄弟
Freak, oh, sticks and stones may break my bones, buddy.
曾经会  现在不会了
Well, they used to. Not anymore.
我会把这个街区都炸了
I'll blow this whole city block.
你知道自己现在也在这个街区内吧
Uh, you do realize you're a part of that block, right?
拜托  老兄  今天是工作日
Come on, man, it's a weekday.
大家只是想安心下班
People just want to get off work,
回家  看电视
go home, and watch the boob tube.
所以你为什么不脱下那件背心
So why don't you take off that vest and--
别碰我
No, don't touch me!
拉尔夫  你还好吗
Ralph, are you okay?
没事
Yeah.
就是心口挺烧的
Yeah, just, uh, wicked heartburn.
新英雄击败珠宝大盗
警告你们这些
Let this be a lesson to all of you
要成为犯罪分子的人
would-be criminals out there.
抓住你们不用我伸展太多
Catching you won't be too much of a stretch.
我们的街道再次安全了
And so, our streets are safe again,
多亏了中城最有趣的新英雄
thanks to Central City's funniest new hero,
弹性人
The Stretchy Man.
好的
Okay.
尴尬
Embarrassing.
西斯科  下一次你和他一起行动
Cisco, next time you're going with him.
爱瑞丝  小鸡迟早得
Iris, a chicken needs
离开窝的
to leave its roost sooner or later,
尤其是当小鸡坚持
especially when that chicken
要单独完成任务的时候
insists on doing his own solo mission.
-很糟  -真的很糟
- This is bad. - This is really bad.
弹性人  糟糕的名字
Stretchy Man, that's a terrible name.
还有  既然我要一直在电视上露面了
Also, now that I'm going to be on TV all the time,
这身灰色的战衣就得换了
this grey suit, got to go.
别乱说  山雀
Hey, easy, chickadee.
不  拉尔夫  糟糕的是你  好吗
No, Ralph, I meant you, okay?
那个炸弹可能会把你炸成碎片
That bomb could have torn you to shreds.
或者乔  或者外面所有的警察
Or Joe, or any of the police outside.
放松  女士们  我的细胞是完全巨和化的
Relax, ladies, my cells are completely polygamized.
-聚合化  -对
- Polymerized? - Yeah, that.
那意味着它们可以伸展并承受炸弹爆炸
Which means they can stretch and take a bomb blast.
-天呐  -德比是无法摧毁的
- Oh, my God. - Dibny is in-dib-structable.
拉尔夫  你没抓到重点
Okay, Ralph, you are missing the point.
你得更小心点
You need to be more cautious.
不不  是你没抓到重点
No, no, no, you are missing the point.
我真正需要的  是一个新的超级英雄名字
What I really need, guys, is a new superhero name.
拉蒙  你这么闲
Ramon, you've had all this time.
就想不到什么吗
You can't come up with anything?
耐心点  好吗  我在想
Patience, okay? I'm getting to you.
只是有些分心
I've just been a little preoccupied,
不知道巴里现在在监狱怎么样了
what with Barry being in prison and all.
你找到什么能证明
You find anything that might prove
迪沃陷害巴里的证据了吗
DeVoe framed Barry yet?
我爸和塞西尔明天去见汉克森法官
My dad and Cecile are meeting with Judge Hankerson tomorrow
来商讨上诉的事
to go over his appeal.
我们已经一点点把证据过了一遍  但是...
We've been pouring through the evidence piece by piece, but...
别担心  爱瑞丝  我们会把他救出来的
Don't worry, Iris, we're going to get him out.
巴里加入过帮派吗
Hey, has Barry joined a gang yet?
我里面有一些朋友
I've got some friends on the inside.
我可以打几个电话
I can make some calls.
闭嘴  拉尔夫
Shut up, Ralph.
好吧
Okay.
我现在不帮忙了
I will stop helping now.
你可以一直盯着钟
You can watch the clock all you want,
但它也不会走得更快
but it won't go any faster.
你是巴里·艾伦对吧  亨利·艾伦的儿子
You're Barry Allen, right? Henry Allen's kid?
我是艾克索·沃克
I'm-- - Axel Walker.
你和你爸绑架过我爸
You and your dad kidnapped my dad once.
没错
Yeah, right.
吃布丁吗
Pudding?
派餐女士多给了我一份  我觉得她喜欢我
Lunch lady gave me extra. I think she has a crush on me.
不是
No.
传闻说  你宰了某位教授
Hey, word on the block is, you carved up some professor.
他给你打了不及格分吗
He give you a bad grade or something?
我没杀人
I didn't kill anybody.
当然  这里所有人都是无辜的
Yeah, sure. Everyone's innocent in here.
特别是那个人  大块头先生
Especially that guy. Yeah, Big Sir.
他真的是无辜的
He's really innocent.
这比平时的要难吃  布丁会变质吗
This is grosser than usual. Does pudding go bad?
艾克索  你想怎么样
Axel, what do you want from me?
做杀人好哥们
To be murder buds.
我们可以分享商业秘密
You know, we could share trade secrets.
我想听听你是如何宰了那个大学骗子的
I'd love to hear how you carved up that college quack.
我在这里不需要任何朋友
I don't need any friends in here.
我觉得不舒服
Oh, man, I do not feel good.
扶他起来
Get him up.
我白净的鞋子被你弄脏了
You got mud on my bright whites.
抱歉  我不是故意的
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
道歉就对了
Sorry's right.
铁山监狱第一周通常是最难熬的  艾伦先生
The first week in Iron Heights is often the hardest, Mr. Allen.
你已经看到几名囚犯
You've already seen what happens
试图制造叛乱的后果了
when a few inmates try to revolt.
适应新生活是需要时间的
Acclimating to your new life will take time.
一向如此  在此期间
Always does. In the meantime,
在这里尽量守规矩
do your best to stay clean in here.
艾伦先生  你一点半的会面时间到了
Oh, and Mr. Allen, your 1:30 is waiting for you.
-很高兴见到你  -我也是
- Hey, I'm so glad to see you. - Me too.
你怎么样
How's it going?
没我想像的那么差
It's not as bad as I thought it would be.
现在在和你说话的
And hey, you're talking to the newest member
可是铁山监狱最新来的保洁人员
of the Iron Heights janitorial staff.
我是现今世上速度最快的拖把
I'm the fastest mop alive.
我们已经全天候在监视迪沃一家
Well, we've been surveilling the DeVoes 24/7.
他们肯定会透露马脚的
I mean, they must have made a mistake somewhere, right?
而且我一直和爸爸反覆地查阅所有的证据
And I've been pouring over all of the evidence with Dad.
我们会把你救出去的  巴里
We are going to get you out of there, Barry.
我知道你们会
I know you will.
其他队员怎么样  我看到拉尔夫上电视了
How's the rest of the team? I saw Ralph on TV.
拉尔夫有点过于骄傲了
Ralph is getting a little cocky.
我刚开始也是  是会这样的
Yeah, I was when I started too-- it happens.
好吧
Yeah.
爱瑞丝  没事的
Iris, it's okay.
只是不敢相信我们的新常态变成这样  巴里
I just can't believe this is our new normal, Barry.
我不想我们的生活变成这样
I don't want this to be our lives.
你会找到证据的
You're going to find something.
我知道
I know it.
时间到
Closing time!
带他们走
Wrap them up!
我只是希望能再握握你的手
I just wish I could touch your hand again.
你会的
You will.
我保证
I promise.
明天见吗
I'll see you tomorrow?
每个明天都会见
Every tomorrow.
沃克吐了他的狱友一身
Walker here spewed all over his cellmate.
说是腹部绞痛
Says he's got cramps.
你是谁  希尔护士呢
Who are you? Where's Nurse Hill?
生病没来  他好像吃了布丁
Out sick. Looks like he ate the pudding.
你怎么知道
Yeah, how do you know that?
因为派布丁的人就是我
Because I'm the one who sent it.
来  艾克索  我们走
Come on, Axel, let's go.
妈
Mom?
沃克和护士逃出去的时候
Walker and the nurse used tranquilizers
给另外两名守卫也打了镇静剂
on two more guards on the way out.
你完全没发现
And nothing tipped you off
这名护士也许是罪犯吗
that this nurse might be a criminal?
她的背景调查完全没问题
Her background check was clean.
她说她叫林赛·法恩哈特
She said her name was Lindsay Fineheart.
她是我们的人力资源公司派来的
She was sent over by our staffing company.
我需要医务室
Well, I'm going to need the hard drive
监控录像的
of the surveillance footage
储存硬盘
from the security cameras in the infirmary.
可惜  铁山监狱还处于模拟信号时代
Well, unfortunately, we're still analog here in Gen Pop.
复制监控带需要点时间
It will take a while to dub the tapes.
在这期间
In the meantime,
我会把法恩哈特的档案拿给你
I'm having Fineheart's file brought down for you.
巴里怎么样
How's Barry doing?
榜样囚犯  就和他爸爸一样
Model inmate, just like his dad.
-我能不能...  -我找找那份档案
- Do you mind if I...? - Let me check on that file.
巴仔
Bare.
乔
Joe, hey.
-你怎么来了  -艾克索·沃克越狱了
- What are you doing here? - Axel Walker escaped.
某个新来的护士帮他越狱
Some new nurse helped him get out.
他进医务室因为吃了布丁
He was in here because of the pudding.
你怎么知道
How do you know that?
他之前在抱怨布丁的味道
He was complaining about the taste.
让我帮忙查这案子吧
Hey, let me help with this, all right?
-巴里  -不
- Barry-- - No.
西斯科想办法绕开监控器的进展如何
Has Cisco having any luck figuring out how to bypass the system?
因为一旦他这么做  我就可以穿墙离开这里
Because once he does that, I could phase out of here.
我就能去追查他的下落
I'm gonna be track him.
巴里  你要暂时待在这里
Barry, you need to stay put for now.
魔术师只是精神不正常的孩子
Trickster is just a messed-up kid.
-我们能搞定他  -我知道  当然
- We can handle him. - No, I know, of course.
我只是已经厌倦了自己无用武之处
I just... I'm already tired of feeling useless, you know?
你在这里要注意的唯一一件事
The only thing you should focus on in here
就是自己小心
is watching your back.
警察不能与犯人有肢体接触
Pretty sure cops can't touch inmates.
不然我会抱抱你
Otherwise, I'd give you a hug.
要坚强  巴仔
Stay strong, Bare.
-警探  -警官
- Detective? - Sir.
这就是她
Well, this is her.
她的名字不叫林赛·法恩哈特
This woman's name isn't Lindsay Fineheart.
她叫佐伊·克拉克
Her name is Zoey Clark.
詹姆斯·杰西有女朋友吗
James Jesse had a girlfriend?
她叫自己恶作剧大师
Yeah, she called herself Prank.
以前  她是杰西的雌雄大盗搭档
Back in the day, she was Bonnie to Jesse's Clyde.
无论是企图谋杀
No matter what, whether it was attempted murder,
纵火还是抢劫  她都跟随在旁
arson, robbery, she was always by his side.
玩具帝国女继承人
炸弹爆炸之后  警察搜找疑犯
那时的人都穿的是什么啊
Man, what were people wearing back then?
佐伊·克拉克曾经是克拉克玩具帝国的受益人
Zoe Clark was the beneficiary to Clark Toys empire.
也算不上是帝国
Not much of an empire.
所有的店铺二十年前均已关闭
All those stores closed 20 years ago.
看来她拥有艺术
Looks like she has Bachelor's degrees
和应用科学的本科学位
in arts and applied sciences,
佐伊·克拉克
恶作剧大师
还有化学硕士学位
as well as a Master's in chemistry.
魔术师和恶作剧大师
Trickster and Prank were responsible for a series
恶作剧大师被抓获
但是同谋仍然在逃
中城一系列恐怖袭击案的罪魁祸首
of terrorist attacks across Central City,
包括破坏加德祖卡口香糖公司
including the destruction of the Gadzooka Bubblegum company.
我一直好奇我最喜欢的口香糖
Huh, I always wondered why
怎么会在九十年代突然消失了
my favorite gum suddenly disappeared in the 90's.
我的地球上还有
We have it on my Earth.
-不可能  -我刚刚说了我们有
- You do not. - I just said we did.
-不可能  -真有
- You do not. - We do.
不管怎样  在杰西被捕之后
Anyway, after Jesse was arrested,
她就消失了
she disappeared.
自此之后  她一直都是逃犯
She's been a fugitive ever since.
看来最后一次见到佐伊的九个月后
Looks like Axel was born nine months
艾克索就出生了
after Zoey was last seen.
我估计她离开去帮助照顾她儿子了
I bet she left to help to take care of her son.
然后她回来劫他出狱
And she came back to bust him out of prison,
然后重新开始
and pick up where she left off.
我在找中城警局的档案
Well, I'm digging into CCPD files
看看她有没有其他已知的同伙
to see if she had any other known associates.
我去给卫星设置搜索网
I'll set the satellite to do a search grid.
-拉蒙  -你给我点你那个
- Ramon? - Hey, how about you hook me up
口香糖行不行
with some of that gum?
你怎么不自己开裂口去拿
Why don't you breach yourself?
-这听起来像是在讽刺我  -算是吧
- That sounds like an insult. - Kind of was.
拉尔夫  你要不要去你的固定位置
Hey, Ralph, do you want to go to your usual spots,
看看你的联系人见没见过她
see if any of your contacts have seen her?
行  我需要个女伴  凯瑟琳  你来
Sure, I need a chaperone. Caitlin, you're up.
快乐时光开始  你付钱
It's happy hour, you're buying.
来吧  用冰霜杀手的信用卡
Come on, use Killer Frost's credit card.
没戏  老兄
No way, Jose.
你以为拉夫尔是钱做的吗
You think Ralphie's made of money?
佐伊·克拉克 恶作剧大师
艾克索·沃克
魔术师
你俩藏在哪呢
Where are you two hiding?
这是什么地方
What is this place?
是克拉克帝国的残骸
It's all that remains of Clarx Toys.
这里可真冷
Oh, it's cold in here.
太棒了
Oh, awesome!
我上了新闻
I made the news, ha!
艾克索·沃克
铁山监狱囚犯在逃
一点也不好  现在警察在找你了
Not awesome. Now the police are looking for you.
等到夜里的时候  咱们早就离开中城了
As soon as night falls, we're out of Central City.
然后咱们和爸爸汇合  对吗
And then we'll go meet up with Dad, right?
这就是你带我出来的原因不是
That's why you broke me out.
因为爸爸想见我  对吗
Because Dad wanted to see me, right?
不完全是
Not exactly.
艾克索  我想让你回到我生活中
Axel, I wanted you back in my life.
好吧  那爸爸怎么办
Right, but what about Dad?
他一年前就逃出去了
Well, he broke out a year ago,
但是他没有来找你
and he hasn't come looking for you.
他不在乎的
He doesn't care.
他当然在乎
Of course he does.
艾克索  你爸爸不行了
Axel, your dad's a deadbeat.
他不想成为这个家族的一员
He doesn't want to be a part of this family,
他也不曾是
and he never did.
别那么说他
Don't talk about him like that.
亲爱的  真对不起  你只是
Honey, I'm sorry, it's just that
没有我那么了解他而已
you just don't know him like I do.
你知道在你长大期间
Do you know what it was like for me
崇拜你爸爸的时候
when you were growing up?
我是什么样的一个生活吗
While you were idolizing your dad?
我那时每天给你做晚餐
I was the one making your dinner.
而只你坐在电视机前看他恐吓整个城市
While you were watching him terrorize the city on TV,
是我开车送你去学校
I was the one driving you to school.
是我确保你做完了功课
I was the one making sure you got your homework done.
是我在大早上给你做好午餐
I was the one packing the lunches in the morning.
-都是我在照顾你  -我知道  妈妈
- I was there for you. - I know, I know, Mom!
好了  现在我们可以让他回来了
Okay, now we can get him back.
我不想让他回来
I don't want him back.
我想让咱俩一起自由生活
I want us to go be free together.
我从来不想让你成为你爸爸那样
I never wanted you to end up like your father.
现在说这个已经太晚了  妈
Well, it's too late for that, Mom.
我只需要让爸爸注意到
I just need to get Dad's attention.
我要让他看到  这个家族里还有人
I'll show him that someone in this family
有着恶搞的天赋  妈妈
still has a funny bone. Mom.
弹力人  中城新任最有趣的人
所有人都安全离开  中城又出现了
Everyone walks away safe, and so Central City
一位新的  更性感的超级英雄
has a new, sexier model of superhero.
我是  我很性感
Me--it's...I'm sexy.
而我知道该怎么做了
And I know just how I'm going to do it.
性感的那个  有人想要签名吗
Sexy one. Anyone want an autograph?
签名  有人要吗
Autograph, anyone?
不要  艾克索
No, Axel.
艾克索
Axel!
听说你今早和一个警察
Heard you had a little one-on-one time
进行了单独会面
with a badge this morning.
天啊
Oh, God.
你先是弄脏了我的鞋
First, you dirty up my shoes.
现在你又在跟警察透口风了
Now, you're snitching to the cops?
你这第一周还真是非同一般啊
You've had quite the first week, haven't you?
我不想惹麻烦
I don't want any trouble.
太晚了
Too late.
这事没完
This isn't over.
谢了
Thanks.
搜索的怎么样了
Hey, how's the search coming?
哈里和我已经设定好了参数
Harry and I already set all the parameters,
只是要在300平方英里中搜查呢
it's just got 300 square miles to comb through, so.
-这可不妙  -你好  中城
- That's not good. - Hello, Central City!
距离上一次我这美丽的脸出现在你面前
It's been far, far too long since my beautiful face
已经过了太久了
graced your screens.
天  这孩子的脸比较适合去做电台
Whoo, this kid's got a face for radio.
魔术师劫持了城市的广播信号
Trickster's hijacking the city's broadcasting signals.
今天  我们要玩一个小游戏
Today, we're going to play a little game
我想称它为  这个能做什么
I like to call what Does This Do
看起来像是个普通的弹力球
Looks like a regular old bouncy ball.
但是它能做什么呢
But what does this do?
-西斯科  -追踪中
- Cisco. - Tracing.
让我们看看你使劲扔它之后...
Let's find out if and when you throw it hard enough...
爆炸
Kaboom!
他在市中心  德米欧与拜尔森转角
He's downtown, corner of DeMeo and Bilson.
把弹性人给我找来
Bring me the Stretchy Man,
不然你们就要被炸飞啦
or else you're gonna go boom boom.
我第一个超级恶棍决斗挑战
My first supervillain thunderdome challenge.
真是太棒了
This is awesome.
拉尔夫  你不了解这个人
Ralph, you do not know this guy.
他很危险
He's dangerous.
他在扔弹力球
He's throwing bouncy balls
穿着一件花哨的扣领短大衣
and wearing a bedazzled pea coat.
我搞得定
I got this.
你还没脱掉那衣服呢啊
You still haven't taken that off, huh?
我穿着它睡觉的
Oh, I sleep in this.
你能用缺口把我送去吗  比较快捷
You mind breaching me there? It's a lot faster.
你在哪  弹性人
Where are you, Stretchy Man?
我这玩意还有好多呢
I've got plenty more where that came from.
战衣不错  翻闹小子
Nice suit, Fall Out Boy.
恶心  你的需要再设计下
Yuck, yours could use some work.
看看这极端的才智
Ooh, look at that cutting wit.
你想要我  我来了
You wanted me, here I am.
太好了  你想玩吗  接住
Great, do you want to play, uh, catch?
你这超级恶棍战斗可真有爆炸性
You're really blowing this supervillain fight.
这是我中城的回归派对
Well, it's my Central City return party.
你的死将会让我成为明星
And your death will make me a star.
小孩玩意
Child's play.
好吧  行  这个我称之为快点喷出来枪
Okay, all right, this is what I call the Hurty-Squirty Gun.
骗到你啦
Tricked ya!
这是强酸  加了点X原料
It's acid, with a little ingredient X.
我叫做酸死你
I call it xid.
战服破损
他在恐慌  心跳极度加快
He's panicking, his heart rate is off the charts.
拉尔夫  你没事吧
Ralph, are you okay?
救命
Help!
烧吧  弹性人  烧吧
Burn, Stretchy Man, burn!
今天可不行  撒旦
Not today, Satan.
他对我做了什么
What the hell did he do to me?
那是些什么玩意
What the hell was that stuff?
艾克索好像造了某种超强酸
Looks like Axel created some sort of super acid.
酸碱值达到负五十
It's got a PH level in the negative 50s,
却只用来烧穿你的皮肤
and all it did was burn through your skin?
天啊  换作普通人
God, if it were anybody else,
就会像异性血液那样熔穿皮肤
it would melt right through them like Xenomorph blood.
就像《异形》一样
Like in...Aliens.
但你说我的是聚合细胞
But you said my cells were polymerized.
我知道
I know...
你说我的细胞坚不可摧
You said nothing could hurt them.
德比  我没那么说  我说你的细胞
Dibny, I didn't say that. I said your cells were bonded
聚合的方式我不曾见过  我没见过这种酸
unlike anything I've ever seen. I've never seen acid like this,
所以没见过的事物我概不负责
and so, cannot be responsible for things I have never seen.
-疼死了  -肯定的
- It definitely hurts. - Mm-hmm, of course.
现在知道你的氪有多大能耐了
Well, now we know what your kryptonite is.
氪是什么东西
What the hell is kryptonite?
-什么  -拜托
- What? - Oh, come on.
我能自愈吗
Think I'm gonna heal?
-可能吧  -最终会的
- Probably. - Eventually.
-可能  -你也知道
- Probably? - Well, you know.
还以为我坚不可摧
I thought I was indestructible.
我们也以为
So did we.
出去
Get out.
好了  凯特琳  你可以处理伤口
Okay, well, Caitlin, you can treat the wound
-帮他止疼吧  -如有需要会的
- and manage the pain, right? - As needed.
好  最重要的是
Okay, well, the most important thing
你安全了
is that you're safe.
拉尔夫  天啊  抱歉
Ralph, oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
艾克索还没抓到
Um, Axel is still out there.
得去找到他  天啊
We should track him down. Um, oh, my God.
可能会有点疼
This might sting a little.
抱歉  我的妻子半小时前
Excuse me, my wife was supposed to be here
就该来了  能麻烦你...
a half hour ago. Could you see if...
好吧
Cool.
我只是好奇你为什么帮我
I was just wondering why you helped me.
因为你爸爸帮过我
Because your dad helped me.
-你还好吧  -不  妈妈  我不好
- Oh, are you okay? - No, Mom, I'm not.
弹性人还活着
Stretchy Man's still alive.
爸只看得到我失败了
All Dad's going to see is that I failed.
他不会想见我的
He won't want to see me.
何必自欺欺人呢  我永远成不了他
Who am I kidding? I'll never be like him.
我觉得你可以比他更强
I think you can be even better than him.
你不觉得  但我有信心
You don't see it, but I do.
你才是真正的魔术师  宝宝
You're the real Trickster, boo-boo.
你这是怎么了
What's gotten into you?
好吧  我没吃药
Okay, I didn't take my meds.
妈  你为我做的吗
Mom, you did that for me?
我会为你做任何事  宝宝
I would do anything for you, boo-boo!
-想跟我一起杀人吗  -就像骑三轮车
- Would you kill with me? - It's like riding a tricycle.
难以忘怀  一起血染城镇吧
You never forget. Let's paint the town red.
我知道该让谁流血
I know whose blood we should use.
只需要新魔术用强力打败"弹力超人"
We just need a new trick to strong-arm Stretch Armstrong.
-不  -不
- No. - No?
我们需要更强的
What we need is something better.
因为我只明白了一件事
Because if there's one thing I've realized,
每个伟大的魔术背后
it's behind every great trick...
都有一位更强的恶作剧大师
is an even better Prank.
各位  魔术师有线索了吗
Hey, guys. Any luck finding Trickster?
乔  地理位置追踪是门艺术
Joe, geo-tracking is an art form.
需要精确  策略和天赐良机
It takes precision, it takes finesse, it takes grace--
根本不需要这些
It requires none of those things.
其实就是他不是超能力者
It's simply the fact that he's not a meta-human.
普通人更难追踪到
Regular humans are harder to track.
就没什么是你觉得有趣的吗
Is there anything you can't suck the fun out of?
窥叶
Leaf peeping.
魔术师
Trickster.
又见面了  中城的各位
Hello again, Central City.
精彩的新节目就要开始了
It's time for the exciting new game show,
"厄运大转盘"
"Wheel of Misfortune."
奖励如此丰盛  还以为自己死了呢
With prizes so amazing, you'll think you died.
如果你们出对了牌  或许能如愿以偿
And if you play your cards right, you just might.
有请主持人  凶残的女酋长
Here's your host, the Murderous Matriarch,
恶作剧大师
Prank!
今晚有什么精彩节目呢
What do we have in store for tonight?
有冷冻表演  惊悚表演和大开杀戒表演
Well, we have chills, thrills, and plenty of kills.
简直是疯子
These guys are absolutely nuts.
那么有请第一位选手
So, why don't we meet our first contestants?
-瞧啊  -瞧啊
- Ta-da! - Ta-da!
还抓了人质
They've got hostages.
准备了惊艳的奖励
Shocking prizes are in store.
恶作剧大师  特等奖是什么呢
Oh, Prank, what about the grand prize?
问得真好
Oh, I'm so glad you asked.
我们准备了强酸淋浴
Because we have an axid shower.
不
Oh, no!
抱歉了  碧波先生
Sorry, Mr. Beebo.
碧波喜欢洗白白
Beebo loves getting clean.
碧波好痛
Beebo has an owie.
-西斯科  -正在三角定位他们的信号
- Cisco. - Triangulating their signal.
得找一位特别贵宾来参加我们的特别演出
We need a special VIP to come down for our special show.
如果你在看  弹性人
So, if you're watching, Stretchy Man,
不如过来转动转盘
why don't you come on down and spin the wheel?
给你一小时  不然这些好人全都得死
You have one hour, or these nice people die.
找到了
There you are.
他们在劳伦斯山的
They're at the old Clark Toys factory
克拉克玩具旧厂
in Lawrence Hills.
赶紧的  弹性人  时间不等人哦
Tick-tock, Stretchy Man. Time's a-wasting.
那么转动轮盘吧
So, let's spin that wheel!
我去让中城警局封锁周围几个街区
I'm going to have CCPD create a perimeter
不让他们逃跑了
a few blocks away, so they can't escape.
哈里  你研制魔术师酸液的
Harry, how are you coming with a solvent
-溶剂进展如何  -进展缓慢
- for Trickster's axid? - Well, slowly.
很难中和某个今天才第一次出现的
Very difficult to neutralize a solvent that hasn't existed
溶剂
until today.
-还有59分钟  -我只需要58分钟
- You've got 59 minutes. - All I need is 58.
拉尔夫  着装准备
Ralph, suit up.
你想要一套新战衣  对吧
Well, you wanted a new suit, didn't you?
我还把它做成了口袋大小
I even made it pocket-sized.
是防酸的吗
Is it axid-proof?
我做不到  各位
I can't do it, guys.
那些人需要我们帮忙
These people need our help.
对  抱歉  但我会被熔掉啊
Yeah, sorry, but me getting melted?
这点有违协议
That is a deal-breaker.
你这么做
Were you only doing this
是因为觉得自己不会受伤吗
because you thought you couldn't get hurt?
不然我为什么要逞英雄
Yeah, why the hell else would I do this?
拉尔夫  去年我也以为自己会死
Ralph, last year, I thought I was going to die, too.
但我没因此止步
But that didn't stop me.
好  那就是我们的差距
Okay, well, that's the difference between us then.
我还没强大到不惧危险
I'm not that strong in the face of danger.
我退出
I'm out.
巴里
Psst, Barry!
拉尔夫  你来这干什么
Ralph, what are you doing here?
我帮你越狱
I'm breaking you out.
拜托  你是英雄
I mean, come on, you're a hero.
穿上紧身战衣  去做英雄吧
Slap on some tights, go be heroic.
拉尔夫  这里到处都是监控器
Ralph, there are cameras everywhere, okay?
我一逃走他们就会知道
They would know within minutes that I vanished.
普通人的一分钟等于你的一小时
So? A minute to us is like hours to you.
穿墙震动出去  去抓魔术师
Just vibrate through the walls, go slap Trickster around,
牢里还没开始送晚餐
and you'll be back before whatever passes for dinner
-你就能回来  -魔术师又做乱了
- in this place. - Trickster attacked again?
对  他和他妈想和我比比
Yeah, he and his mommy want to tussle with me,
但我的原则是不跟
but I have a rule against fighting terrorists
有恋母情节的恐怖分子打架
with an Oedipus complex, so.
这像是闪电侠的工作
This looks like a job for the F-L-A-S-H.
不好意思  区别是
I'm sorry, why is this different?
到目前为止你对抗坏蛋做得都不错
You've done a good job handling bad guys so far.
我受伤了
I got hurt.
艾克索合成了某种酸  而我们推测
Axel created some kind of acid that, we're guessing,
那可能会杀死我
can probably kill me.
我还没准备好死
I'm not ready to die.
这个工作
Look, this job,
会让你觉得自己战无不胜
it has a way of making you feel invincible.
但每隔段时间
But every once in a while,
死亡就会来拜访
a little mortality check shows up.
我很努力想忽视这种感觉  但
I've been trying so hard to ignore this feeling, but...
我不像你那样无所畏惧
I'm not fearless like you are.
拉尔夫  我也不是无所畏惧
Ralph, I'm not fearless.
我每天在这牢房里醒来
I mean, I wake up every day in this cell,
感到我没有办法帮助别人
and feel like there's nothing I can do to help anyone.
这吓坏我了
And, I mean, that terrifies me.
我之前是施救的人
I used to be somebody who saved,
现在  我就是巴里·艾伦
and now I'm just Barry Allen.
囚犯编号  3562
Inmate number 3562.
-那我带你出去  -我不是这个意思
- So let me spring you. - That's not my point.
有帮助别人的能力  但什么也不做
Having the ability to help someone, but do nothing.
这种死亡
That is a far worse death
比魔术师给你造成的更可怕
than anything that Trickster has for you.
但克服恐惧  拯救生命
But rising above that fear and saving those lives,
是更伟大的人生
that's a greater life.
所以  克服它
All right, so rise up.
我认为那对你来说不算什么
I don't think it's a stretch for you.
你真的相信我能做到
You really believe I can do it?
对  你只需相信你自己
Yes, you just need to believe in yourself.
你知道怎么出去吧
Hey, you know your way out of here, right?
嗯
Yeah.
你们有一个小时
You got one hour!
扫瞄读取到屋顶有个像集装箱的东西
Scans are reading some kind of container on the roof.
看来看是新的
It looks new.
镀锌钢
Galvanized steel.
这就是他们装尼扎替丁的地方
That's where they're keeping the axid.
好  我会中和它
All right, I will neutralize it.
你俩营救人质
And you two guys, you get the hostages out.
我们需要冰雪女王
Oh, we're gonna need the ice queen.
不是这样的  我不能就
Oh, that's not how it works, I can't just--
莱克西·洛什
Lexi La Roche!
是小时候欺负她的人
It was her childhood bully.
有好多压抑的怒火
There's a lot of repressed anger in there.
走吧
Let's go!
天呐  开始吧
Oh, boy, here we go.
谢谢  大块头
Thank you. Big Sir.
我爸在这救了你  对吧
My dad saved your life in here, didn't he?
这就是你帮我的原因
That's why you helped me out.
怎么救的
How?
我肚子疼了好几天
I had stomach pains for days.
你爸发现了  发现是阑尾要胀破了
Your dad found me, figured my appendix was about to burst.
监狱里的医生晚上不在
Prison doctors were gone for the night.
他们不可能及时赶回来
There's no way they could have made it back in time.
但亨利医生说服了沃夫监狱长
But Doc Henry convinced Warden Wolfe
进行了手术
to do the surgery.
他主刀救了我
He operated and saved my life.
所以这是你欠他的
And that's why you owed him.
现在我们扯平了
Now, we're even.
大块头
Big Sir.
记着这里任何看起来好玩的都可能致命
Okay, Remember, anything in here that looks fun is probably lethal.
-就像我  -不错
- Just like me. - Nice.
把这些送货人送到安全的地方
Okay, let's deliver these delivery people to safety.
或者不管他们  杀掉魔术师和恶作剧大师
Or we could just leave them and kill Trickster and Prank.
还记得我们谈过
Remember that talk about
杀出一条血路的话题吗
murdering your way out of problems?
-我们不那么做  -暂时而已
- Yeah, we don't do that. - Yet.
我们带你们出去
We're going to get you out of here.
碧波饿了
Ooh, Beebo hungry.
碧波喜欢玩耍
Beebo likes to play.
碧波
Beebo--
骗你们啦
Tricked ya!
我猜那计划没用吧
I'm guessing the plan didn't work?
救命
Help!
哈里  是陷阱  他们抓了凯特琳和西斯科
Harry, it's a trap. They've got Caitlin and Cisco.
-我这就出发  -不  你别去
- I'm on my way. - No, you're not.
我去
I am.
那你会用到这个的
Then you're going to need this.
妙极了
Groovy.
放开他
Leave him alone.
我说过你会后悔的
I told you you'd be sorry.
你不会两次都中
You won't get lucky twice.
虎父无犬子
Like father, like son, eh?
哈里  你到房顶了吗
Harry, are you on the roof yet?
到了  尼扎替丁也在
Yes, and so is the axid.
好吧
All right.
你得中和尼扎替丁
You need to neutralize the axid.
我们没时间了
We're running out of time.
谢谢了  我知道
Yep, thank you, I'm aware of that.
我们要一个英雄
Now, we asked for one hero.
但现在  我们有俩
But now, we've got two!
是时候决一雌雄了
It's time for our Showcase Showdown,
转动那个转盘  看看有什么有趣的奖品
so let's spin that wheel, and see what fun prize
在等着我们的新朋友
awaits our new friends.
哈里  拜托你成功了
Harry, tell me you've got it.
还没有
Don't got it.
快  我好多年没杀过人了
Hurry up, I haven't killed anyone in years.
酸桶挑战
平局
Oh, a tie.
我想他们就一起死吧
Hmm, I guess they die together.
装束不错
Nice outfit.
谢了  我有个好裁缝
Thanks, I've got a great tailor.
放了他们  恶作剧的家伙
Now let everyone go, pranksters,
这样就不会有人受伤
and no one gets hurt.
我们以为你怕了呢  弹性人
We thought you chickened out, Stretchy Man.
没错  我之前是怕了
Actually, I did.
我以为我是战无不胜的
See, I thought I was pretty much invincible
直到你和你的大号水枪
until you and your oversized water pistol
在我的心中种下恐惧
put the fear of God in me.
不客气
You're welcome.
我都准备放弃了
And I was ready to throw in the towel.
但我拜访了一位朋友
But then I visited a friend of mine.
他帮我意识到没人是无惧的
And he helped me remember that no one is fearless.
但真正的英雄能克服恐惧
But real heroes, they find a way to rise above that fear
无论如何都能有所不同
and make a difference anyway.
即使在过程中牺牲
Even if it kills them in the process.
所以这就是克服恐惧的我
So, this is me, rising up.
希望不会牺牲
Hopefully without the dying part.
现在放了我的朋友
Now let my friends go.
首先  说得不错
First of all, great speech.
深受鼓舞  熔化我心
So inspired, it melted my heart.
谢谢  我来的路上想的
Oh, thank you, I worked on it on the way over.
现在熔化你的吧
Now let's melt yours.
射他  宝宝
Shoot him, boo-boo!
宝宝
Oh, boo-boo!
我要是你就放弃了
I'd give up if I were you.
熔化你的朋友如何
How about I melt your friends instead?
-哈里  快  -我还没搞定
- Harry, now. - I don't got it.
哈里
Harry?
不
No!
和你的朋友们说再见吧
Say good-bye to your little friends!
哈里
Harry!
不疼
It doesn't hurt.
居然一点都不疼
我没死
I'm not dying!
我为什么没死
Why am I not dying?
因为我及时搞定了
Because I got it.
太好了  干得漂亮  伙计们
Yes, nice work, guys!
我活下来了
I'm going to live, whoo!
我都没想过逃跑
Oh, don't even think about running.
随时效劳  好了
Any time. Okay, uh...
你们有带剪刀吗
you got scissors anywhere?
知道俗话怎么说的吗  警探
You know what they say, detective?
一起杀戮的家人才能团结一致
The family that slays together stays together.
-没错  在监狱里  -得了吧
- Yeah, in prison. - Hey, come on.
你可没法关一位魔术师太久
You can't keep a Trickster behind bars for long.
那我们就走着瞧吧
Oh, we'll see about that.
你真的太棒了  我们能在十到十五年内
You were amazing. Can we do it again
-再来这么一次吗  -宝宝
- in 10 to 15 years? - Boo-boo.
我两年内就能让我俩越狱出去
I'm going to break us out of here in two.
给我老老实实上车待着
Get in the damn car.
你真的单枪匹马制服了魔术师
Is it true that you took down Trickster and Prank
和恶作剧大师吗
single-handedly?
你当超级英雄多久了
How long have you been a superhero?
你是单身吗
Are you single?
没错  约一小时  我当然是单身
Yes, about an hour, oh, hell yes.
-你喜欢吃虾吗  -不喜欢
- Do you like shrimp? - No.
但我肯定中城的居民
But I'm sure the people of Central City
会非常感激你的  弹性人
would love to thank you, Stretchy Man.
我不叫这么个名字
That's not my name.
那该叫你什么  毕竟你确实有弹性
Then what should we call you? I mean, you do stretch.
不  我不是有弹性  我是可以扭曲
No, I don't stretch, I contort.
我有弹力  我可以伸缩
I elasticize, I elongate, man.
伸缩人
The Elongated Man?
只是措辞不同
It was just an expression.
-确实有一定的  -我不知道
- It has a certain... - I don't know.
-有点"妙不可言"  -我也挺喜欢的
- "Je ne sais quoi" to it. - I like it, too.
我讨厌这名字
Well, I hate it.
也许你应该让我来给你起名
Well, maybe you should have let me do the naming.
没错
Exactly.
别担心  你会有机会的
Oh, don't worry, you'll get your chance.
这个名字是不可能固定下来的
There's no way this is going to stick.
很可能会固定下来
Probably gonna stick.
伸缩人  拜托  太直白了
The Elongated Man? Please, it's so literal.
你们觉得普林斯会愿意被人叫
You think Prince would have settled
矮个子吉他男吗
for Shorty Guitar Man?
不可能
No way.
奥克兰的婚庆乐队  普林斯为乐队成员
像"紫人乐队"一样  我也需要
And like The Purple One, I too need something
名字里暗示我性感的本质
that hints at the true depth of my sexy nature.
-比如闪电侠这种名字  -没错
- Like The Flash. - Exactly.
他是位极速者  在几秒钟内搞定一切
He's a fast operator, gets the job done in seconds.
或者像是冰霜杀手
Or Killer Frost.
我还能说什么呢
What can I say?
有了能力  就得名副其实
When you got it, you got it.
你确实名副其实
You got it.
乔
Hey, Joe.
我该怎么做
What should I do?
不惜一切代价保护这座城市就行了
Man, do whatever it takes to keep the city safe.
就像我们其他人一样
Just like the rest of us.
这我可以接受
I could live with that.
看来我可以再多照顾你一段时间了
Guess I'll be looking out for you a bit longer.
我拔刀相助可不是因为想得个人情
I didn't get involved because I wanted a favor,
我只是想帮你一把
I just wanted to help.
给你个建议  你要想在这生存下去
Piece of advice, you want to survive in here,
找个朋友吧
find a friend.
你父亲一定很为你骄傲
Your father would be very proud of you.
谢谢
Thanks.
我爸也叫你大块头吗
Did my dad call you Big Sir?
不  他叫我戴夫
No, he called me Dave.
艾伦  有人来看你了
Allen, you've got a visitor.
你跟拉尔夫说的话肯定是起作用了
Well, whatever you said to Ralph must have landed.
他冒着生命危险救下了凯特琳和西斯科
He risked his life to save Caitlin and Cisco,
多亏了你那番话
thanks to you.
我只是把他心中也有的信念激发了出来而已
I just brought out what was already inside of him.
你似乎能激发很多人心中的信念
You seem to have that effect on a lot of people.
怎么了
What?
原来待在监狱里
Just turns out being in here
和待在外面也没有那么不同
isn't so different from being out there.
除了我们不能在一起
Except we're not together.
我都不能触摸你
And I can't touch you anymore.
咖啡
Coffee,
当英雄就这点回报
that's all I get for being a hero?
那你还想要什么  一块曲奇饼吗
What do you want, a cookie?
那我倒是不介意来一块
Ooh, don't mind if I do.
不是吧  哥们
Come on, man.
戴面具的问题就在于
The thing about wearing a mask
甚至没人知道你是好人
is no one even knows you're a good guy.
现实就是这样  孩子
Them's the breaks, kid.
好极了  我的果汁饮料到了
Ah, yes, there's that delicious nectar.
顺便谢谢你请我喝咖啡
Hey, thanks for getting this coffee, by the way.
谁请  我吗  我没钱
Who, me? I'm broke.
我甚至都没带钱包
I didn't even bring my wallet with me.
-我压根就没有钱包  -你是认真的吗
- I don't even own a wallet. - Are you serious?
-每次都是艾伦请客  -天呐
- Allen always pays. - Oh, my God.
别担心
No worries.
总是把爱心传递出去
Uh, always pay it forward.
这是我的座右铭
That's my motto, you know?
因为任何特定情况下
Because at any given moment,
我们都有可能需要援手
one of us could need a helping hand.
比如现在  你们完全是陌生人
Like now, you two total strangers,
没有带现金  于是就有人
you know, were short on cash, and then someone just
突然出现毫无征兆地帮了你们一把
steps out of the blue and helps out in a totally random way,
我说得对吗
am I right?
这不仅仅是因果循环
And you know, it's more than just karma.
这是无限的因果轮回在我们生活中
It's the principle of infinite consequence
发生作用的原理
at work in our lives.
而这种因果总在不断膨胀
And it's always expanding.
在无限叠加的基础上进行正向求和
Creating positive sums on an infinite basis.
很令人称奇对不对
Isn't that amazing?
-确实  -你知道什么令人称奇吗
- Yes? - You know what's amazing?
你的衬衫相当令人称奇
That shirt's pretty amazing.
是的  谢谢  没错  这是件经典款
Yeah, thanks, yeah, it's a classic.
俄勒冈之旅  我超喜欢这个游戏
Oregon Trail? I love this game.
祝你们一天愉快
Have a great day.
好了
Okay.
漂亮美好的女孩  而拉尔夫·德比
A nice, beautiful girl, and Ralph Dibny
并没有请她一顿美味的海鲜自助
doesn't offer her a delicious crustacean buffet?
我觉得她太聪明了我配不上她
Mmm, I think she's too smart for me.
拉尔夫·德比居然有自知之明了
Self awareness from Ralph Dibny?
那我觉得你还是有希望的
I think there's hope for you yet.
这叫能屈能伸
That's a stretch.
所以我们是要在那定格吗
Is that where we freeze frame?